免责声明 1/2：
所有由我录制的游戏画面均使用了我自行编译的Eaglercraft版本，该版本基于我购买的正版Minecraft。
任何指向已编译完成的Eaglercraft版本的URL均被故意模糊处理。
我不支持或鼓励任何人下载或游玩盗版Minecraft。
Did you know that you can simply open a single HTML file
你知道你可以直接打开一个HTML文件或网页URL，在网页浏览器中立即玩到完整的Minecraft Java版
or web URL and instantly Play the full version of Minecraft Java Edition in your web browser
Yep you can
是的，你可以做到
But should you do this
但你应该这样做吗？
Well my lawyer told me to say no
我的律师告诉我不能
And put this disclaimer on screen
并且要将免责声明提示出来
免责声明 2/2：
本视频是为教育和信息目的而创建，旨在讨论名为Eaglercraft的软件。
视频中的内容提供用于批判性分析、评论和报道目的。
视频中包含的材料根据美国版权法第17编第107条“合理使用”的指导原则使用。
本视频不支持或推广未经授权使用Minecraft或任何相关软件。
So take that as you will
所以，请自行斟酌
But regardless I'm going to tell you the story about how a very dedicated developer
我很乐意讲述这位非常敬业的开发者如何让Minecraft Java版完全在网页浏览器中运行的故事
made Minecraft Java Edition run entirely within a web browser
How became insanely popular and all the controversies that came with doing that
以及如何变得非常流行和随之而来的所有争议
Especially when it came to Mojang's lawyers which is why I'm taking a huge risk when uploading this video
特别是涉及到Mojang的律师时，这就是为什么我在上传这个视频时冒了很大的风险
But I'm doing it for you guys
但为了你们做了这个视频 (●'◡'●)
So let's get to it
那就开始今天的故事
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
翻译基于自动生成的英语字幕，如不准确，请在弹幕或评论区打出你认为正确的翻译
It all started with a player by the name of lax 1 dude
一切的开始就要从一个名叫 lax 1 dude 的玩家开始讲起
in 2020, he thought it would be really cool to somehow make Minecraft work in a web browser again
2020年，他认为让我的世界再次在网页浏览器中运行会非常酷
Because as of 2016 running regular Java Minecraft
因为在2016年之后，现代网页浏览器不再支持运行常规的Java版我的世界
in a modern web browser is no longer supported
So his idea was to get the entire game to run using JavaScript
所以他的想法是使用JavaScript让整个游戏运行起来
Now the JavaScript programming language which is different from regular Java
现在的JavaScript编程语言与常规的Java是不一样的
Can in fact run in a web browser
可以在网络浏览器中运行，并且至少以某种形式被用于互联网上98%的网站
and is actually used in at least some form on 98% of websites on the internet
Even my own website uses JavaScript
即使是我的网站也使用了JavaScript
If he could somehow pull this off it would be an incred incredible feat of Minecraft engineering
如果他能完成这件事，那将是我的世界工程学上的一个令人难以置信的壮举
So lax went to work. to get Minecraft Java to run on JavaScript
lax开始制作。要让我的世界Java版在JavaScript中运行，整个游戏必须通过一个名为TeaVM的工具进行编译
the entire game would have to be compiled with a tool called TeaVM
Which essentially makes regular Java applications work in JavaScript
这个工具使得常规的Java应用程序能够在JavaScript环境中运行
But it unfortunately wasn't that simple
但遗憾的是，事情并没有那么简单
if you know anything about programming your program will usually require dependencies which are basically
如果你对编程有所了解，你会知道你的程序通常会依赖于一些外部库或模块，这些被称为依赖项
它们基本上是你的程序运行所依赖的其他代码片段
pieces of other code that your program depends on to be able to run
it's kind of like ingredients when baking a cake you depend on eggs being in your recipe
这有点像烘焙蛋糕时的原料，你需要依赖食谱中的鸡蛋
Otherwise your cake won't set properly
否则蛋糕就无法做成
One of those ingredients or dependencies that Minecraft needs is something called LWJGL
我的世界所需的一个依赖项是名为LWJGL的库
which is the primary backbone of the entire game. without it Minecraft will not run at all
它是我的世界的主要支柱。没有它，游戏根本无法运行
You see the problem is that LWJGL cannot be compiled with TeaVM
问题在于LWJGL无法通过TeaVM进行编译
Even worse Minecraft versions 1.6 and above required even more dependencies than just that
更糟糕的是，我的世界1.6及以上版本需要的依赖项还要更多
So for his first version of the project
对于他的第一个项目版本
he compromised with using Minecraft version 1.5 as his guinea pig
选用我的世界1.5版作为他的实验对象
Which was originally released all the way back in 2013
这个版本最初是在2013年发布的
Now lax's solution with getting LWJGL to work was to spend an entire month manually rewriting the entire dependency from scratch
现在，Lax的解决方案是花费整整一个月的时间，手动从头开始重写整个LWJGL依赖项
To have compatibility with TeaVM therefore making it work in JavaScript
为了使其与TeaVM兼容，从而在JavaScript中运行
But this was only one of the many issues he had to deal with
但这只是他必须解决的众多问题之一
Other issues included having to get the graphics to work properly
其他问题包括需要正确处理图形，解决由JavaScript引起的延迟问题，通过重写游戏的多个部分来修复这些问题
fix lag issues caused by JavaScript by rewriting multiple parts of the game
And making servers function properly it took many months of programming and testing
并且确保服务器正常运行，这需要数月的编程和测试
But near the end of 2020 the fully ported web version of Minecraft 1.5
但在2020年底，他称之为Eaglercraft的完全移植的网页版我的世界1.5版本基本上已经完成且变得相当稳定
which he called eagler craft was pretty much complete and mostly stable
A few years later in May of 2022
几年后的2022年5月
lax decided to step up his game with eaglercraft and update to Minecraft release 1.8
Lax决定升级Eaglercraft，将其更新到我的世界1.8版本
He chose this version to update to because it was his favorite
他选择这个版本，因为这是他最喜欢的版本，并且在许多我的世界服务器上仍然有广泛的支持，包括Hypixel
and there was still wide support for it on many Minecraft servers including Hypixel
But this of course required even more dependencies that
但这当然需要更多的依赖项，他必须修改这些依赖项以使其在JavaScript中正常工作
he would have to modify to make work on JavaScript
Plus many other modifications where if I discussed all of them
此外，还有许多其他修改，如果我要讨论所有这些修改，那将会非常详细
This video would be way too long
这个视频将会变得很长
So another developer by the name of ayunami2000
另一位名为ayunami2000的开发者也会在Lax遇到困难时提供帮助
would also help out where LAX would otherwise get stuck
ayunami2000增加了语音聊天+其它额外功能
Also keep in mind that all of this work on making eagler craft 1.8 was done in secret
还要记住，所有这些关于制作Eaglercraft 1.8的工作都是秘密进行的
As Lax didn't want to make false promises if they couldn't end up getting it to work
因为Lax不想在最终无法使其工作时做出虚假的承诺
But they eventually pulled it off and it took over 7 months to
但他们最终成功了，花费了超过7个月的时间
Lax called this version of eaglercraft EaglercraftX
Lax将这个版本的Eaglercraft称为EaglercraftX
Now of course I have to explain why this project was called eaglercraft to begin with
当然，我需要解释为什么这个项目最初被称为Eaglercraft
Basically when Lax was in Middle School
基本上，当Lax还在中学时
he thought it would be funny to develop a secret language
他认为开发一种秘密语言会很有趣
是的，这张表全是lax 1 dude 做的
One of the words in his language was eagler which means someone who eats eagle eggs
在他的语言中，有一个词是eagler，意思是吃鹰蛋的人
And was meant to be used as an insult
并且这个词是用来作为侮辱的
Lax knew that if eaglecraft got popular most of the player base would be middle schoolers
Lax知道，如果Eaglecraft变得流行，大部分玩家将会是中学生
So he named his browser Port of Minecraft after eagler from his middle school secret language
因此，他以中学秘密语言中的eagler命名了他的Minecraft浏览器端口
In hopes that would enter the everyday language of other middle schoolers
他希望这将成为其他中学生日常语言的一部分
This dream would eventually become a reality
这个梦想最终成为了现实
观察“eaglercraft”的谷歌搜索如何与上学季节相对应
as eaglercraft became insanely popular with students in middle school
因为Eaglercraft在中学学生中变得非常流行
And would typically refer to eaglercraft as just eagler
并且通常会将EaglerCraft简称为Eagler
Now there's many reasons why eagler ccraft became so popular
现在有很多原因可以解释为什么EaglerCraft变得如此流行
The first thing is pretty obvious it's free and open source
第一个原因很明显，它是免费的并且开源的
But of course the legality of that is quite questionable
当然，这种做法的合法性是相当有争议的
As we all know what happened to Minecraft forfree.com
正如我们都知道的，Minecraftforfree.com发生了什么
*HAF：关于这个网站的视频，站内已有人翻译*
The only difference now is instead of Notch playing Quake over the whole ordeal
现在唯一的区别是，不再是Notch在整个事件中玩Quake
Minecraft is owned by a multi-billion doll company
Minecraft现在属于一家拥有数十亿美元资产的公司，并且有数十亿美元的公司律师支持他们
with multi-billion dollar company lawyers to back them
And we'll be talking a lot about that shortly
我们很快会详细讨论这一点
The second reason why eagler craft is so popular is that it's extremely accessible
Eaglercraft之所以如此受欢迎，第二个原因是它极其易于访问
Searching Google for eaglercraft will show you
在Google上搜索Eaglercraft会显示大量托管Eaglercraft客户端的网站
a plethora of websites that host the eaglercraft client
And because it's open source, anyone can just copy the code to their website
因为它是开源的，任何人都可以复制代码到他们的网站
and now they're hosting an instance of eaglercraft
现在他们正在托管一个Eaglercraft的实例
In fact Lax's intentionally designed eaglercraft to run locally from a single HTML file
事实上，Lax有意设计Eaglercraft使其能够从单个HTML文件本地运行
That's less than 15 megabytes in size
Eaglercraft的单个HTML文件大小不到 15 MB
For comparison just the assets of regular Minecraft 1.8 are over 100 megabytes
相比之下，常规Minecraft 1.8的资源文件大小就超过了100 MB
The way this was done was by removing everything unnecessary in compressing what was
这是通过移除所有不必要的内容并压缩剩余部分来实现的
For instance all of the music for the game was removed
例如，游戏中的所有音乐都被移除了，声音和一些纹理也做了压缩处理
and the sounds and some of the textures had compression added to them
Now because eaglercraft can be played locally from a file
由于Eaglercraft可以从本地文件运行，也意味着它甚至可以在不访问互联网上的托管网站的情况下进行游戏
it also means that it can even be played without going to a website hosted on the internet
This is why eaglercraft is so popular with school students
这就是为什么Eaglercraft在学生群体中如此受欢迎的原因
As the it departments usually block these kinds of websites
由于学校的IT部门通常会屏蔽这些类型的网站，这反而激发了一些学生的兴趣
on school Wi-Fi which triggered a few of them
使用Google管理控制台阻止Eaglercraft在学校的Chromebook上运行
Now aside from dodging school it admins eaglercraft is also popular
除了躲避学校IT管理员的限制外，Eaglercraft还因其几乎可以在任何硬件上运行而受欢迎
because it can play on almost any hardware
Including Chromebooks that a lot of schools now provide to students
包括现在许多学校提供给学生的Chromebook
But other people got creative and I've also gotten the game
但其他人很有创意，我也成功让游戏在一些家用电器上运行，比如三星冰箱
to launch on appliances like a Samsung fridge
and even a Tesla Model X
甚至在一辆特斯拉Model X上
*现在展示的是Model Y
Only problem is you can't really connect a mouse and keyboard to a car
唯一的问题是，你不能真正把鼠标和键盘连接到汽车上
so you couldn't actually move around in a world
所以你不能在世界中移动
Regardless I wonder what Hardware people will try to run eaglerCraft on next or should they
无论如何，我想知道人们接下来会尝试在什么硬件上运行Eaglercraft，或者他们是否应该这样做
I guess that brings me to the legality part of this whole project
我想这让我想到了整个项目的合法性部分
Obviously eagler craft distributed in its compiled form certainly breaks the Minecraft EULA
显然，以编译形式分发的Eaglercraft确实违反了我的世界最终用户许可协议
as it says in quote you must not distribute anything we've made
正如引述中所说，你不得分发我们制作的任何东西
But Lax thought of this
但Lax了解到了这一点
For eaglercraftX he had the idea to mimic projects like Minecraft mods
他的想法是模仿我的世界模组这样的项目
by publishing his code in the form of patches that are applied to the games code
通过补丁的形式发布他的代码，应用于游戏，而不是仅仅非法上传完整的反编译我的世界1.8源代码到互联网上
instead of just illegally uploading a full copy of the decompiled
Minecraft 1.8 source code to the internet
But in practice this didn't really end up working
但实际上，这并没有奏效
Because basically all the websites that hosted eaglercraft
因为基本上所有托管Eaglercraft的网站最终都分发了整个编译后的副本
distributed the whole compiled copy anyways
and of course it wouldn't be long until Mojang had enough
当然，不久之后，Mojang就会采取行动，开始打击Eaglercraft
and would start cracking down on eaglercraft
In November of 2022 the first recorded MCA takedown request
2022年11月，第一个与Eaglercraft相关的数字千年版权法案删除请求发送给一个中国Eaglercraft服务器
for anything eaglecraft related was sent to a Chinese eaglecraft server
by an agency called app detex who have a contract with Mojang's parent company
由一家名为App Detex的机构发出，该机构与Mojang的母公司签订了合同
Microsoft that allows them to submit dmca takedown requests on their behalf
微软允许他们代表其提交DMCA删除请求
Now for those who don't know what a dmca takedown request is
现在，对于那些不知道什么是DMCA删除请求的人来说，DMCA代表数字千年版权法
dmca stands for Digital Millennium Copyright Act
which is a US law that protects copyright owners from illegal copying of their software
这是一项美国法律，旨在保护版权所有者免受其软件的非法复制
and the dmca takedown requests are formal notices
而DMCA删除请求是发送给潜在侵权者的正式通知，要求他们移除相关内容
sent to potential offenders requesting to remove the content
they claim is being used illegally
他们通常声称这些内容正在被非法使用
Usually if you don't comply with the request the owners
通常情况下，如果你不遵守删除请求，版权软件的所有者仍可能对你采取法律行动
of the copyrighted software could take legal action against you
Anyways this dmca takedown of that Chinese server
无论如何，这次针对中国服务器的DMCA删除请求让Lax感到意外，他不想冒险
took Lax by surprise and he didn't want to take any chances
So he decided to delete his GitHub repository for eaglercraft
因此，他决定删除他的GitHub上的Eaglercraft仓库
but of course he let people know beforehand thus giving
但他事先通知了人们，因此给了超过2000人机会去Fork这个项目
the chance for over 2,000 people to Fork the projects
which ended up making it pretty annoying for Mojang to dmca every single one
这最终使得Mojang对每一个Fork进行DMCA删除请求变得相当麻烦
Shortly after Lax deleted the entire project from his GitHub account
不久之后，Lax从他的GitHub账户中删除了整个项目
Successfully putting it out of Mojang's reach
成功摆脱了Mojang
Or so he thought just a few days later Lax found himself inundated with dmca takedown requests
只是他这么认为，仅仅几天后，Lax发现自己被DMCA删除请求淹没
This time coming directly from Mojang's headquarters
这次直接来自Mojang的总部
First on his GitHub account for a copy of a Minecraft Beta 1.3 version of eaglercraft
首先针对他在GitHub账户上的一个我的世界Beta 1.3版本的Eaglercraft副本，他忘记删除了
that he forgot to delete
Then on some of his websites that hosted eaglercraft and on some Google Drive links he shared
然后是他在一些托管Eaglercraft的网站上，以及他分享的一些Google Drive链接
Lax also found out that two dmca were even sent to his ISP due to him hosting eaglerCraft on it
Lax还发现，由于他在其上托管Eaglercraft，他的ISP甚至收到了两份DMCA通知
*ISP：网络服务提供商*
and on top of all of this Mojang allegedly contacted Discord and had his server deleted
除此之外，据称Mojang还联系了Discord，并要求删除他的服务器
and his account terminated in response
他的账户被封禁，作为回应，Lax决定从这些来源中永久删除所有Eaglercraft内容
Lax decided to permanently remove all of the eagle aircraft content from those sources
as you don't want to mess with dmca requests
不想处理DMCA请求
Now after all of this Lax would abandon eaglercraft
在这一切之后，Lax决定放弃Eaglercraft，毕竟他所做的是违反版权法的行为
after all what he was doing was breaking copyright law
and Mojang was firing back hard
Mojang下手太狠了
It was time to give up retire quit
是时候放弃，隐退，落幕了
Yeah no
当然不 (￣へ￣)
Despite multiple takedown requests
尽管收到多次下架请求
Lax got right back to work on eaglecraft continuing to edit on a GitHub alternative called gitlab
Lax 在eaglecraft项目上立即重新投入，继续在名为 GitLab 的 GitHub 替代平台上进行
and improving it even more
并且进一步改进
Until Mojang contacted gitlab and demanded that
直到 Mojang 联系了 GitLab，并要求删除他所有的仓库和账户
all of his repositories and account should be deleted
So pretty much from here the cycle of dmca takedowns
从这里开始，Eaglercraft 的 DMCA 下架和重新上传到其他平台的循环就不断重复着
and re-uploading of eagler craft to other platforms continued over and over again
which included Lax's own postings as well as multiple
其中包括 Lax 自己的发布以及多个 Eaglercraft 服务器、项目的分支
eaglercraft servers and forks of the project
At this point Mojang was sending out so many dmca takedown requests
在这一点上，Mojang发出如此多的 DMCA 删除请求，以至于他们的法律团队甚至创建了一个模板，以便发送给涉嫌侵权者
that their legal team even created a template for dmca takedown
requests to send to suspected offenders
In total Lax received eight dmca takedown requests and possibly
Lax 总共收到了8份 DMCA下架请求，可能还有数百份请求是以任何方式或形式托管 eaglercraft 的人发出的
hundreds more were handed out to others hosting eaglercraft in any way shape or form
Even countless YouTube videos talking about eaglercraft
即使无数关于 Eaglercraft 的 YouTube 视频也被 DMCA 了，所以上传这个视频
were DMCA so by me uploading this video
I'm taking a massive risk myself
我冒着巨大的风险
At this point it was very obvious that Mojang wanted eaglercrafts to be gone
在这一点上，很明显 Mojang 想要 Eaglercraft 消失
So as one final attempt to appease Mojang
所以作为最后一次尝试来安抚 Mojang
Lax created a repository on his GitHub account with a message to Mojang
Lax 在他的 GitHub 账户上创建了一个仓库，并向 Mojang 发送了一条消息
offering them the source code to eagler craft for official use on minecraft.net
提供他们 EaglerCraft 的源代码，以便在minecraft.net上正式使用，理由是 EaglerCraft 在低端硬件如 Chromebook上运行良好
with the reason being that eagler craft runs so well on low-end Hardware like Chromebooks
which could be useful for use in the official game
这可能对官方游戏的使用非常有帮助
but unfortunately Mojang didn't respond to this
但不幸的是，Mojang 没有对此作出回应，可能是因为他们对此不感兴趣
probably because they just weren't interested
Now at this point, you may be wondering if anything
现在此时，你可能在想这些 DMCA 删除请求是否真的有任何结果
actually came out of all of these dmca takedown requests
Well turns out not as Mojang hasn't actually sued anyone over eaglercraft yet
结果是，Mojang 还没有因为 Eaglercraft 起诉过任何人
I'm not a lawyer so I can only speculate as to why this is the case
我不是律师，所以我只能推测为什么会出现这种情况
it could be the fact that Lax refuses to accept any money whatsoever for his project
这可能是因为 Lax 拒绝为他的项目接受任何资金
After all Lax told me that the only reason he's still working on the eaglecraft project
毕竟，Lax  告诉我，他继续进行 Eaglercraft 项目的唯一原因是他喜欢挑战在网页浏览器中运行我的世界
is because he just likes the challenge of making Minecraft run in a web browser
That's it
就是这样
So if there's no financial gain behind it Mojang
所以如果没有经济利益，Mojang 可能会将其视为对他们威胁较小
may see that as a lesser threat to their bottom line
Although other websites hosting eaglercraft making money off ads may be a different story
尽管其他托管 Eaglercraft 的网站通过广告赚钱可能是另一回事
So that's the story of eaglercraft for now who knows what will happen to it next
所以这就是目前 Eaglercraft 的故事，谁知道接下来会发生什么
Maybe eaglecraft will update to an even later version of Minecraft
也许 Eaglercraft 会更新到更高版本的我的世界
Unless Mojang shuts it down before then
除非 Mojang 在那之前将其删除
原标题：The Story of Eaglercraft  原作者：SalC1    原视频上传日期：2024年5月8日
So I guess I'll just have to be keeping my eagle eyes on this project
所以我想我只能密切关注这个项目
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
一分钟的字幕制作大概需要五分钟的时间，喜欢本视频请免费支持一下 ( •̀ ω •́ )✧